<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Storytellers of Canada Disclaimers</title>
    <link>https://radioapp.storytellers-conteurs.ca/tos/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Storytellers of Canada Disclaimers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://radioapp.storytellers-conteurs.ca/tos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://radioapp.storytellers-conteurs.ca/tos/posts/privacypolicy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radioapp.storytellers-conteurs.ca/tos/posts/privacypolicy/</guid>
      <description>Effective Date: 19-02-2021
Your privacy is important to us It is Storytellers of Canada&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to the Storytellers of Canada App (hereinafter, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;www.storytellers-conteurs.ca/&amp;quot;). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (&amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo;) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms Of Service</title>
      <link>https://radioapp.storytellers-conteurs.ca/tos/posts/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radioapp.storytellers-conteurs.ca/tos/posts/tos/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Storytellers of Canada App These terms of service outline the rules and regulations for the use of Storytellers of Canada&amp;rsquo;s App.
By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms of service in full. Do not continue to use Storytellers of Canada&amp;rsquo;s website if you do not accept all of the terms of service stated on this page.
The following terminology applies to these Terms of Service, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements: &amp;ldquo;Client&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Your&amp;rdquo; refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Company&amp;rsquo;s terms of service.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
